[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The average temperature around the world has climbed during the previous century due to global warming by this much.", "correct_answer": "1 degree Fahrenheit", "incorrect_answers": ["3 degrees Fahrenheit", "4 degrees Fahrenheit", "2 degrees Fahrenheit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Do vampire bats ever roost alone?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year were the first Grammy Awards given?", "correct_answer": "1959", "incorrect_answers": ["1958", "1960", "1961"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Academy Award-winning European-born director produced and directed the drama movie Bitter Moon, starring Peter Coyote?", "correct_answer": "Roman Polanski", "incorrect_answers": ["Emir Kusturica", "Milos Forman", "Pedro Almodovar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After World War II, this country was split into two states which were not reunited until 1990.", "correct_answer": "Germany", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "Spain", "Austria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The state of Oregon in entirely in the Pacific time zone.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "American athletes Dave DeBusschere, Gene Conley and Del Rice all have what in common?", "correct_answer": "They played pro basketball and pro baseball", "incorrect_answers": ["They played pro baseball and  pro football", "They played pro basketball and pro football", "They played pro basketball and became team owners"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does a person who has a gymnophobia fear?", "correct_answer": "Nudity", "incorrect_answers": ["Closed spaces", "Rivers", "Bright colours"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Cars, when Lightning McQueen first entered Radiator Springs, Filmore was staring at a stoplight with Sarge. Which blink did he say was slower?", "correct_answer": "3rd", "incorrect_answers": ["1st", "4th", "2nd"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Before the release of the The Blair Witch Project, the actors in the film were listed as missing and presumed dead on the popular movie website IMDb (Internet Movie Database).", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When did the The Longest Day war drama come out?", "correct_answer": "1962", "incorrect_answers": ["1959", "1963", "1964"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress portrays Sally in the 1989 romantic comedy movie When Harry Met Sally...?", "correct_answer": "Meg Ryan", "incorrect_answers": ["Melanie Griffith", "Jodie Foster", "Julia Roberts"]}]